Guide to the Cornell University Board of Trustees Presidential Search Committee records, 1962-2014.
Cornell University Board of Trustees Presidential Search Committee records, 1962-2014.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Cornell University Board of Trustees Presidential Search Committee records, 1962-2014.
2-6-1872
Cornell University. Board of Trustees. Presidential Search Committee.
2.4 cubic feet.
Correspondence, reports.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Records of the Presidential Search Committee and other materials associated with Presidential searches at Cornell University.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Records of the Presidential Search Committee and other materials associated with Presidential searches at Cornell University. Includes files relating to the searches of James Perkins, Dale Corson, Frank H. T. Rhodes, Jeff Lehman, David Skorton and Elizabeth Garrett, including minutes of meetings and correspondence concerning the work of the Trustee Committee and faculty and alumni advisory committees. Much of the material relating to Perkins, Corson and Rhodes are the files of Board of Trustee and Search Committee member Austin Kiplinger.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Cornell University.; Corson, Dale R.; Garrett, Elizabeth.; Kiplinger, Austin H., 1918-2015; Lehman, Jeffrey S.; Perkins, James Alfred, 1911-1998.; Rhodes, Frank Harold Trevor; Skorton, David J.; Cornell University -- Presidents.; Cornell University
Subjects:
Presidents
INFORMATION FOR USERS
Access Restrictions:
Restricted to permission of the University Counsel's Office.
CONTAINER LIST
- 1962-1969, Files relating to the 1962 (James Perkins) and 1969 (Dale Corson) presidential search (Box 1, Folder 0)
- List, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  Lists of candidates, other nominations and new nominations, November and December 1976
- List, 1976-1977 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  Lists of candidates, December 1976-January 1977
- Files on Individuals, 1965-1977 (Box 1, Folder 3-10)
  Photocopies of notes, assessments from sources contacted by the Search Committee 1977, short vita, reports, reports, papers, clippings, nomination forms
- Candidate files A-B, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Candidate files B-C, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Candidate files C-D, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Candidate files D-G, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Candidate files H-K, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Candidate files K-M, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Candidate files M, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Candidate files M-O, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Candidate files O-R, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Candidate files R-S, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Candidate files S-W, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 21)
- Candidate files W-Z, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  Also miscellaneous Austin Kiplinger correspondence
- Presidential Search Committee files, 1976-1977 (Box 1, Folder 23)
- Presidential Search press reports, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 24)
- Presidential searches at other universities (Box 1, Folder 25)
- Cornell Presidential Search Committee, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 26)
- Files pertaining to the search for Jeff Lehman, 2002 (Box 1)
- Files pertaining to the search for David Skorton, 2005 (Box 2)
- Files pertaining to the search for Elizabeth Garrett, 2014 (Box 3)